[{"id": 1484, "question": "\"No man is an island\" is a well-known line from John Donne's Devotion. It was written more than three hundred years ago. Even now people still agree with him. No one can live a completely lonely life. Without other people, life will become empty and sad. We all need to have friends. For some of us, although making friends is not difficult, feeling shy, we may not want to make the first move. It is also difficult at times to keep the friends we already have. There are many books about friendship, but Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, written in 1936, is the most famous. This \"how to\" book about getting along with other people became a best seller. It was later put into 28 languages. Dale Carnegie's advice seems to be simple, but can his advice help you? Do you need to...\n\nQ: The best title for the passage should be   _  .", "options": ["How to Make Friends", "A Famous Book", "Friendship First", "John Donne and Dale Carnegie"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 375, "question": "My friend Mike was shaking his head in disbelief. \"That young woman who just waited on me,\" he said, pointing to an employee of the fast food restaurant where we were eating, \"had to call someone over to help her count change. The cash register showed her I needed 99 cents, but she couldn't figure out how to count out the coins.\" I understood Mike's concern. What we have done is to create several generations of individuals most of whom have no idea how to reason; how to do simple math; how to do research; or, finally, how to be creative . The reason for this is our overuse of information technology: video games, television, digital watches, calculators, and computers. Information technology feeds us information without requiring us to think about it and let us perform operations without un...\n\nQ: What's probably the author's suggestion about children's problem?", "options": ["To get them off TV and computer games.", "To teach them how to learn from video games.", "To turn off all electronic equipment at school.", "To give them freedom in the use of computers."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2930, "question": "Kodak's decision to apply for bankruptcy protection is a sad, though not unexpected, turning point for a leading American corporation that pioneered consumer photography and dominated the film market for decades, but finally failed to adapt to the digital revolution. Although many attribute Kodak's downfall to \"complacency ,\" that explanation doesn't admit the efforts with which the company went to reinvent itself. Decades ago, Kodak invented the first digital camera in 1975 -- but in a fateful decision, the company chose to focus on its traditional film business. Large companies have a difficult time switching into new markets. For example, although Kodak predicted the rise of digital photography, its culture was too rooted in the successes of the past to fully welcome the future. In the ...\n\nQ: What was Kodak's major mistake?", "options": ["Its blind faith in traditional photography.", "Its failure to see Fuji photo's action.", "Its refusal to sponsor the 1984 Olympics.", "Its overconfidence in its own culture."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1452, "question": "When Caleb Forbes got his first job at an advertising company at the age of 20, he thought he would be at the company for years. But after seven months he was bored. Soon after that, Forbes moved to London. He took four different jobs at three companies over the next five years. Forbes wanted a better job and higher pay---he was never quite satisfied. Welcome to the world of a job hopper. Forbes's story isn't unusual these days and such frequent movement from one job to the next will become more common. The main reason: the nature of employment is changing. There are a lot more contracts and part-time jobs or flexible employment. That leads to people having a greater number of jobs. What's more, layoffs and pay freezes , among other things, have pushed people from one job to another. In so...\n\nQ: Employers usually think those who left their former job in a short time   _  .", "options": ["can do their new work better", "are hard-working and easy-going", "have more experiences", "will quit their new job again after a short time"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 727, "question": "Expensive and new gloves allow chatterboxes to take the term \"handsfree\" to a new level--by talking into them as they make a call. The gloves are known as \"Talk to the Hand\" and cost PS1,000 a pair. They fixed a speaker unit into the thumb and a microphone into the little finger that can be connected to any mobile handset using Bluetooth. Artist Sean Miles designed the new gloves that double as a phone in part of his project that shows the possibilities of gadget(,) recycling. He uses outdated gloves and combines them with parts from mobile handsets recycled through _ , which commissioned the project. Mobile phone users will be able to keep their hands warm while they chat without taking their phones out of their pockets or handbags. Mr Miles designed two pairs of the new gloves--one in pi...\n\nQ: The purpose of the project is to   _  .", "options": ["promote the technology of IT", "enable people to talk to their hands", "raise people's awareness of recycling", "attract visitors' attention in the exhibition"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1202, "question": "In a world with limited land, water and other natural resources, the harm from the traditional business model is on the rise. Actually, the past decade has seen more and more forests disappearing and the globe becoming increasingly warm. People now realize that this unhealthy situation must be changed, and that we must be able to develop in sustainable ways. That means growth with low carbon or development of sustainable products. In other words, we should keep the earth healthy while using its supply of natural resources. Today, sustainable development is a proper trend in many countries. According to a recent study, the global market for low-carbon energy will become three times bigger over the next decade. China, for example, has set its mind on leading that market, hoping to seize chan...\n\nQ: The traditional business model is harmful because of all the following EXCEPT that   _  .", "options": ["it consumes natural resources", "it makes the world warmer", "it brings severe damage to forests", "it makes growth hard to continue"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1968, "question": "For some people, the prospect of starting college, especially going away to school, is scary. It's probably the first time that you'll be totally responsible for your own schedule. What if you intend to go to college but just don't feel ready to start yet-for whatever reason-and you don't want to take on a full-time job after graduation? You might want to take a year off to pause and regroup. This practice is common in some countries, like the United Kingdom, where it's called a \" _ \". Taking time off doesn't mean you should ignore the idea of applying to college. In fact, you may want to consider making your college plans before you become involved in other things, especially if you'll be travelling. Apply to schools and make your choice, then ask for a deferred admission. Rachel took a y...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Taking Time Off", "Disadvantages of a \"Gap Year\"", "Plans after Graduation", "How to Apply to College"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2793, "question": "It was 7:00 am in Kyoto, Japan, and the taxi company had just called a second time to say they couldn't find my house. Once again I spelt out directions even a blind person could follow. I glanced impatiently at my watch, and waited. Only two hours remained until my flight left--and it was an hour and a half trip to the airport. Outside, heavy rains were pouring down. My house was so far north in the city that buses pass only here times a day. The telephone rang again. \"Terribly sorry,\" began the man at the taxi company. Then I realized that the taxi company, flooded with calls, could only offer in-city runs. I had heard this happens when the weather gets bad. I shouted into the phone that I had a plane to catch and I would meet the taxi outside my house. Standing in the wind-driven rain, ...\n\nQ: The writer got to the airport   _  .", "options": ["by riding in Mike's car from the taxi company", "with the help of Mike from the post office", "by getting a lift in a passing car", "with the help of a taxi driver sent by his company"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 787, "question": "When Chinese student Du Juan brought her American boyfriend home two years ago to use the toilet, her Japanese roommate became so upset that she shouted in English: \"I hate you.\" Du, then 21 and an undergraduate at Bridgewater State College in Massachusetts, was shocked. So was her boyfriend. \"Later I realized that she didn't literally mean what she said and that she was not aware of the full meaning of the word 'hate' in English,\" said Du. \"It was more a problem with translation,\" she added. Cultural differences can cause confusion about what words or even actions mean, an issue that has come to the forefront recently following the arrest of a Chinese doctoral degree student in New Jersey. Zhai Tiantian, who studied at the Stevens Institute of Technology, has been accused of trying to set...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements about Zhai Tiantian is true?", "options": ["He set fire to a campus building.", "He argued with a professor because he received a low mark.", "He has received a doctor's degree at the Stevens Institute of Technology.", "He is facing a serious charge because he murdered the professor."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 123, "question": "If you go into the woods with your friends, stay with them. If you don't, you may get lost. If you do get lost, this is what you should do. Sit down and stay where you are. Don't try to find your friends -- let them find you. You can help them to find you by staying in one place. There is another way to help your friends or other people nearby to find you. Give them a signal by shouting or whistling three times. Stop. Then shout or whistle three times again. Any signal given three times is a call for help. You will be helped by others. Keep up the shouting or whistling, always three times together. When people hear you, they will know that you are not just making noise for fun. They will let you know they have heard your signal. They will give two shouts, two whistles or two gunshots. When...\n\nQ: If you feel thirsty when you are lost in the forest, what should you do?", "options": ["Go and find a brook.", "Light a fire and make yourself some tea.", "Go to find a brook and leave marks behind you.", "Find something to hold the water."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1247, "question": "Billy's favorite color is orange. But he can't see what orange looks like. Billy is blind. A month after he was born, his mother noticed that his eyes weren't quite as big as a normal baby's.\"Billy would never be able to see.\" the doctor told his mother. After that Billy's mother began talking to him, describing things she saw outside the window. She described everything to him. Billy does not only depend on his mother's descriptions to learn about the world around him. He sees with his ears and his hands, too. He has perfect hearing. When people make phone calls, he can tell the numbers they dial . Billy loves computer science. He began teaching himself computer programming when he was just seven years old. His dream school would be Stanford University. He gets top grades in his classes, ...\n\nQ: When did Billy begin teaching himself computer programming?", "options": ["When he was7 years old.", "When he was in Seven Grade", "When he was high school", "When he was at university"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3376, "question": "New rules for pubs and clubs, including a ban on drinking games like the awful \"dentist's chair\", will be introduced in Britain this year to prevent the heavy drinking culture, which costs the country billions of pounds a year. Other activities like \"all you can drink for 10 pounds \", \"women drink free\" nights and speed drinking competitions will also be banned. But, on the other hand, offers of cheap alcohol in supermarkets will not be affected, which is widely regarded as one of the main sources of Britain's problems with under-age and over-drinking. Doctors and health experts argue that the government has failed to use its most effective weapon, the taxation of minimum price controls on alcohol. Home Secretary Alan Johnson said that the government and the industry had a duty to act on h...\n\nQ: New rules for pubs and clubs will be introduced in Britain to ban heavy drinking because   _  .", "options": ["people drink too much without paying taxes", "drinking games are infamous", "drinking competitions are very crazy", "drinking in the country costs too much"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3074, "question": "In our daily life, many of us feel stressed more or less. Some like this pressure and work better because of it. Others are not comfortable with any stress at alls they soon become unhappy if they feel stressed. Sometimes stress can lead people to do things they wouldn't usually do, such as overeat, smoke, drink, or use drugs. Streas, however, is a very normal part of life. It is important to understand that stress doesn't come from an event itself, that is, from the things that are happening in our lives. It comes from the meaning we give to what has happened. For example, a crying baby may be stressful to one person, but it may not bother another person at all, a traffic jam may be stressful to one person while another person may be able to stay calm. We can experience stress any time we...\n\nQ: What does the author suggest dealing with stress?", "options": ["Finding the cause and making changes.", "Controlling the emotions", "Having enough sleep", "Taking some drugs"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3480, "question": "A few years ago, I moved into a new house in Los Angeles. Soon after, a family moved in next door. It wasn't the best of times for me. I had just divorced from my second wife, and I wasn't working. I'd come home each day and sit by myself in the backyard. One night, I heard someone from the yard next door, \"Tom ! How are you, Tom? \" I couldn't see anybody through the trees, but I answered, \"I' m good.\" \"Good!\" said the voice. \"What's your name?\" I asked. \"Eric.\" Then I heard someone say, \"Eric, don't bother him.\" \"Okay!\" Eric said. \"Talk to you tomorrow!\" Months later, on Halloween, we finally met face to face. Eric came to the door dressed like a rap star. We became friends. We'd hang out in our yards, and Eric, who was almost 17 at the time and look liked a 13-year-old, would tell me his...\n\nQ: What do we learn about the writer when he had just moved into his new house in Los Angele?", "options": ["He often came back very late.", "He was working in the city at that time.", "He and his second wife had just gotten divorced.", "He often talks with others in the backyard."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 568, "question": "Opportunity knocked on my door last January when I was given a chance to work in another country. At first, it seemed really scary for me to live on my own. But I had to overcome the true challenge! Luckily, I met seven new friends, six boys and one girl. They were really nice and I loved their company. We hung out most weekends. We cooked, watched movies, chatted and shared jokes! It was amazing -- until something unexpected happened ! One of my friends was diagnosed with kidney stones which needed to be removed as soon as possible. But our friend could not afford the surgery. He tried to get help from our other friends but they refused him. My heart cried for him! Our friends abandoned him just when he needed them most. I didn't know how to help him because I didn't have any money either...\n\nQ: What does the author intend to tell us by sharing his story?", "options": ["We should not judge a person by his look.", "Trouble can put one's qualities to the test.", "True friends should share in joys and sorrows alike.", "We can't depend on friends when in trouble."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1023, "question": "Did the iPod kill music ? DID Steve Jobs kill the music industry? That's the question on many people's lips since rock star Jon Bon Jovi accused the apple boss of personally destroying the music industry. Bon Jovi centers his criticism on how he believes music downloading has robbed young people of what he calls the \"beauty of buying on album\", \"Kids today have missed the beauty of taking your allowance money and making a decision based on the _ , not knowing what the record sounded like,\" he said. But far from killing the industry, many young people today think Jobs has been a blessing , offering you instant, and selective access to a whole world of music. Keith Staskiewicz at Entertainment Weekly speaks for the feelings of many music lovers. He believes listening to Mp3s rather than reco...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements might Keith Staskiewicz agree with according to the article?", "options": ["Records or CDs shouldn't be sold in stores any more.", "Steve Jobs and Apple are partly to blame for destroying the music industry.", "There are surely more ways to enjoy music than on iPods.", "Music downloading has its advantages and is a change that should be accepted."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3380, "question": "New rules for pubs and clubs, including a ban on drinking games like the awful \"dentist's chair\", will be introduced in Britain this year to prevent the heavy drinking culture, which costs the country billions of pounds a year. Other activities like \"all you can drink for 10 pounds \", \"women drink free\" nights and speed drinking competitions will also be banned. But, on the other hand, offers of cheap alcohol in supermarkets will not be affected, which is widely regarded as one of the main sources of Britain's problems with under-age and over-drinking. Doctors and health experts argue that the government has failed to use its most effective weapon, the taxation of minimum price controls on alcohol. Home Secretary Alan Johnson said that the government and the industry had a duty to act on h...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Heavy drinking will be banned in Britain.", "Over-drinking will be taxed.", "Drinking in Britain will be banned.", "12 billion pounds is spent on drinking."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1128, "question": "The U. S. Postal Service (USPS) is losing billions of dollars a year. The government company that delivers \"small mail\" is losing out to email and other types of electronic communication. First-class mail amount fell from a high point of 104 million pieces in 2000 to just 64 million pieces by 2014. Congress permits the 600.000-empIoyee USPS to hold a monopoly over first-class and standard mail. The company pays no federal, state or local taxes; pays no vehicle fees; and is free from many regulations on other businesses. Despite these advantages, the USPS has lost $52 billion since 2007, and will continue losing money without major reforms. The problem is that Congress is preventing the USPS from reducing costs as its sales decline, and is blocking efforts to end Saturday service and close ...\n\nQ: What do we know about the USPS?", "options": ["Its great competitor is the delivery firm FedEx.", "It is an old public service open to competitions.", "Its employees don't pay federal, state or local taxes.", "It has complete control of first-class and standard mail."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2913, "question": "Most young people enjoy some forms of physical activities. It may be walking, cycling or swimming, or in winter, skating or skiing. It may be a game of some kind, football, hockey, golf, or tennis, it may be mountaineering. Those who have a passion for climbing high and difficult mountains are often looked upon with astonishment. Why are men and women willing to suffer cold and hardship, and to take risks on high mountaineering? This astonishment is caused probably by the difference between mountaineering and other forms of activity to which men give their leisure. Mountaineering is a sport and not a game. There are no manmade rules, as there are for such game as golf and football. There are, of course, rules of a different kind, which would be dangerous to ignore, but it is this freedom f...\n\nQ: The main difference between a sport and a game lies in origin of the   _  .", "options": ["uniform", "activity", "skills", "rules"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3208, "question": "People want action on noise, a recent public meeting in Brisbane showed.Some want technical improvements such as quieter air conditioners or better sound barriers around major roads.Others want tougher laws to restrict noise from building sites or to require owners to take responsibility for barking dogs.But the highest priority was a noise complaints system that works. Brisbane City Council receives more complaints about noise than all other problems put together.So it conducted a survey and found that about half its residents are upset by noise in one form or another -traffic, mowers, pool pumps, air conditioners or loud parties.This inspired the Council to bring together more than 100 citizens one evening to talk through a range of options. The meeting found the present regulatory syste...\n\nQ: What does the word \"run-round\" (Para.3) mean?", "options": ["Unfair treatment.", "Quick response.", "Delaying action in response to a request.", "Full attention."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2948, "question": "Animals can be extremely protective of their young. But when hard times call, animal fathers can be really a danger to their own kids. Daddy Lion A combination of laziness, pride, cruelty and anger makes the lion one of the most fearsome and worst dads of the animal kingdom. When not walking proudly across the jungle, the father lion just lazes around under the sun, or waits for one of its lioness partners to bring back food. Once the lioness gets home the food, the lion eats up most of it, and leaves little or nothing at all for the kids. The father doesn't even train the kids for hunting and surviving, it is the lioness who teaches them how to _ themselves. The Polar Father Cute, pure and soft. Protective of young ones and family? Sure. But what makes the polar bears one of the worst dad...\n\nQ: The lion and the polar bears are similar in   _  .", "options": ["searching food all by themselves", "letting the mothers take care of the kids", "letting the mothers eat up the food", "wanting to train the kids to be cruel"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 313, "question": "The computers and the Internet The computer is one of the most important inventions of today. Ever since it was invented, it has changed our lives a lot. People can do a lot of things with the computer. For example, some software can be used too help people finish their work. If one can't finish it at once, the computer can save it so that one can find it quickly the next time. When you talk about computer, you must mention the Internet.. The Internet is a huge worldwide collection of computer networks. A network is a small group of computers working together. You can find information about almost any topic in the world from this network.. For example, you can use the Internet instead of a library to find information about current issues for your homework. You can also find information abo...\n\nQ: With the help of the internet,  _  .", "options": ["You can find information about almost any topic in the world from this network..", "You needn't to go to the library to find information about current issues for your homework.", "You can talk to your friends or even do some shopping.", "You can also find information about your favorite pop or film stars"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1721, "question": "Computer technology is still developing rapidly. The computer of the future will continue to increase in value and performance while decreasing in cost. It will become smaller, but faster and more powerful. It is possible to make some guesses about what the future of the computer will look like, based upon the types of technologies that are being developed now. A lot of progress has already been made in some of these new technologies, but some are still in their earliest stages and may not be ready for use for years. Two of the most interesting areas of computing that are currently being developed are quantum computing and nanotechnology . Quantum computing is one possibility for the future of the computer that could make computers run far faster than even the quickest computers do today. ...\n\nQ: The text is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["what nanotechnology is", "what quantum computing is", "what the future of the computer is", "what future computers can bring us"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1730, "question": "George Bernard Shaw and Winston Churchill disliked each other. It is said that the playwright once sent Churchill two tickets for the opening night of one of his plays, together with a card, which said, \"Bring a friend (if you have one).\" Churchill, however, returned the tickets with a note, which said, \"I shall be busy that evening. Please send me two tickets for the second night (if there is one).\" There is no record of whether Shaw ever sent the tickets....\n\nQ: What was Shaw trying to say to Churchill on his card?", "options": ["Churchill should not go to the play alone.", "Churchill should not bring too many people.", "Churchill may have to waste the two tickets.", "Churchill did not have any friend."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2813, "question": "Trees are useful to man in three very important ways: they provide him with wood and other products, they give him shade, and they help to prevent drought and floods. Unfortunately, in many parts of the world man has not realized that the third of these services is the most important. In his eagerness to draw quick profit from the trees, he has cut them down in large numbers, only to find that without them he has lost the best friends he had. Two thousand years ago a rich and powerful country cut down its trees to build warships, with which to gain itself an empire. It gained the empire but, without its trees, its soil became hard and poor. When the empire fell to pieces, the country found itself faced by floods and starvation. Even though a government realizes the importance of a plentifu...\n\nQ: In the writer's opinion,    _   , or the forests will slowly disappear.", "options": ["measures must be taken", "people shouldn't draw benefit from the tree", "government must realize the serious results", "unless trees never be cut down"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1415, "question": "Water is the most common substance found on the earth, but less than 1% of the earth's water is suitable for drinking. More than 1,000,000,000 people around the world survive on just over 1 galon of water a day. Probebly more than 3,000,000,000 people may suffer from not having enough water by the year 2025. You are considered lucky if you live in a country where you can drink water out of your kitchen tap or bathroom tap. People in some countries have to pay for drinking water at home. So clean water is one of our most valuabe natural resources . In fact, peole waste so much clean water today. In factories lots of water is wasted. At home many people are not taking showers but still baths, and many are brushing their teeth with the tap turned on. Children are no longer taught how to save ...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage   _  .", "options": ["when man can't live without water", "where there is no water resource", "why there is less water on the earth", "how important it is to save water"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 754, "question": "Do you like chocolate? Maybe most people do. A box of it can be a great gift. Buy one for a friend and give it as a surprise. See how happy that person gets. Say you just got a box of chocolate. Which piece do you pick first? A man has studied people's choices. He says they tell something about the person. Did you choose a round piece? You are a person who likes to party. Did you choose an oval shape? You are a person who likes to make things. Picking a square shape shows something else. The person is honest and truthful. You can depend on him or her. What kind of chocolate do you pick? Maybe you like milk chocolate. This shows you have warm feelings about the past. Dark chocolate means something else. A person who chooses it looks toward the future. What about white chocolate? Would you c...\n\nQ: If you enjoy eating milk chocolate you may   _  .", "options": ["look forward to the future", "like to think of the past", "enjoy parties and fun", "have trouble making decisions"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2192, "question": "American schoolchildren often wear uniforms if they attend religious or other private schools. Most public schools do not require uniforms. But over the last ten years or so, more of them have moved in that direction, including high schools. Students may have to wear a specially purchased uniform. Or they may just have to dress alike~for example, white shirts and dark color1ed pants or skirts. Even schools that do not require uniforms generally have a dress code or other rules about what they consider acceptable. Policies commonly ban clothing that shows offensive images or words, or simply too much skin. Items like hats may be not permitted because ,for example, different color1s may be connected with violent gangs. Some parents like the idea of uniforms. They say it means they do not hav...\n\nQ: Some parents are against uniforms because they think  _", "options": ["the government goes against the civil laws", "they probably waste an extra amount of money", "the dress code often appears impolite to others", "the uniforms cost much less than they really do"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2141, "question": "Skin - diving is a new sport today. This sport takes you into a wonderful new world. It is like a visit to the moon. When you are under water, it is easy for you to climb big rocks because you are no longer heavy .Here, under water, everything is blue and green. During the day, there is plenty of light. When fish swim nearby, you can catch them with your hands.When you have tanks of air on your back, you can stay in deep water for a long time. But you must be careful when you dive in deep water. To catch fish is one of the most interesting parts of this sport. Besides, there are more uses for skin - diving. You can clean ships without taking them out of water. You can get many things from the deep sea. Now you see that skin -diving is both useful and interesting....\n\nQ: Skin- diving is a new sport. It can take you to  _  .", "options": ["the moon", "a new world of land", "the mountains", "deep water"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 688, "question": "Dear John, My name is Amber and I want to share my story with you because what you've shared about life and positive energy has changed my life. This past year has been one of the hardest for me. I felt I was stuck in a position that had nothing to do with what I wanted to do with my life. In January, after two years of being together, my boyfriend left me. I read your blog every morning as I drink my coffee at work, but it wasn't until this March that I told myself \"no more negativity\" as you taught readers in your blog. Since then I've got into new habits at work to keep my energy positive. When people walk in the front door, I'm the first face they see, so I smile big when I say \"good morning\" to them, especially on Mondays. Instead of waiting for someone to ask me for help, I offer it ...\n\nQ: What does Amber's change tell us?", "options": ["Practice makes perfect.", "Bad luck doesn't exist long.", "A positive attitude is rewarding.", "A friend in need is a friend indeed."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 404, "question": "The literal meaning of philosophy is \"love of wisdom\". But this meaning does not tell us very much. Unlike the other disciplines ,philosophy cannot be defined by what you study, because it is actually unlimited. Anything can be the subject matter of philosophy: art, history, law, language, literature, mathematics, medicine, psychology, religion, science, and values. Philosophy is one of the world's oldest subjects of study, and in fact, the other academic disciplines are directly related to philosophy. For this reason you get a Doctorate of Philosophy (Ph.D.) in biochemistry, or computer science, or psychology. Two broad sub-fields of philosophy are logic and the history of philosophy. Logic is the science of argument and critical thinking. It provides sound methods for distinguishing good...\n\nQ: With the study of philosophy, you can  _  .", "options": ["become a great leader", "succeed in everything", "find a good job soon after graduation", "make progress in your career development"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1186, "question": "A recent study, published in last week's Journal of the American Medical Association, offers a picture of how risky it is to get a lift from a teenage driver. Indeed, a 16-year-old driver with three or more passengers is three times as likely to have a deadly accident as a teenager driving alone, while the risk of death for drivers between 30 and 59 decreases with each additional passenger. The authors also found that the death rates for teenage drivers increased sharply after 10 p.m., and especially after midnight. With passengers in the car, the driver was even more likely to die in a late-night accident. Robert Foss, a scientist at the University of North Carolina Highway Safety Research Center, says the higher death rates for teenage drivers have less to do with \"really stupid behavior...\n\nQ: A suggested measure to be taken to reduce teenagers' driving accidents is that  _  .", "options": ["driving in the presence of an adult should be made a rule", "the licensing system should be improved", "they should not be allowed to drive after 10 p.m.", "they should be forbidden to take on passengers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2186, "question": "Linda and Lucy were best friends. They graduated from high school and went to the same college for further studies. After some days Linda found that her friend was behaving strangely. She would remain quiet, sleep too much and turn wild, very often. At first, Linda thought it was just because of the problems she had met in her studies. However, Lucy became even stranger over time. Finally, Linda couldn't take it any longer and asked Lucy about her strange behavior. Lucy broke into tears and said that she was going around with a boy, who was taking drugs and forcing her to take them, too. Linda was shocked by her story. She then advised her friend to leave the boy. She reminded Lucy of her dreams of becoming a successful doctor and encouraged her to set an example for others. She also remin...\n\nQ: What course did Linda and Lucy mainly study in college?", "options": ["Medicine", "Science", "Law", "Art"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2398, "question": "European Work Experience Program(E.W.E.P.)is an independent British organization which began in 1991 in the city of London.E.W.E.P.provides the opportunity for students from the 25 countries of the European Union and nationals from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein to live in England,to gain work experience,to practice their English and to get a better insight into the British social and eulturallife. To apply you must meet the following requirements: *Preferred age: 18 to 28 years old *Be able to work in the UK for a period of at least two months. *Must have a good knowledge of English. *Due to work permit restrictions,European Work Experience Program Ltd will only select you if you are a European Union Member or national from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein. Europ...\n\nQ: What's the purpose of writing the text?", "options": ["To introduce a new program in England.", "To attract more students to work in England.", "To describe the working conditions in England.", "To make clear the requirements for students working in England."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3347, "question": "In cities with rent control, the city government sets the maximum rent that a landlord can charge for an apartment. Supporters of rent control argue that it protects people who are living in apartments. Their rent cannot increase; therefore, they are not in danger of losing their homes. However, the critics say that after a long time, rent control may have negative effects. Landlords know that they cannot increase their profits . Therefore, they invest in other businesses where they can increase their profits. They do not invest in new buildings which would also be rent - controlled. As a result, new apartments are not built. Many people who need apartments cannot find any. According to the critics, the end result of rent control is a shortage of apartments in the city. Some theorists argu...\n\nQ: There is the possibility that setting maximum rent may_.", "options": ["cause a shortage of apartments", "worry those who rent apartments as homes", "increase the profits of landlords", "encourage landlords to invest in building apartment"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3415, "question": "I am a professor of sports and exercise so I often deal with nervousness in my research with sports people. Actually, most people experience nervousness at some time or another. If you are feeling anxious, my advice is to first find the cause or causes. Make a list of those things that are making you nervous and work out which ones you can do something about. Focus all of your efforts on managing the causes that you can control. Most people cannot tell the difference between controllable and uncontrollable causes, so things they can't control become a big reason for nervousness. Dealing with this is very important if people want to keep a healthy mind. Simply try to accept the uncontrollable causes of nervousness. You might be worried about the weather on a big day, an accident or an attac...\n\nQ: Who wrote this passage?", "options": ["A reporter.", "A sportsman.", "A patient.", "A professor."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3184, "question": "Instagram is a fast,beautiful and fun way to share your life with friends and family.Take a picture or video,choose a filter to transform its look and feel.and then post to Instagram--it's that easy.You can even share to Facebook.Twitter and more.It's a new way to see the world.So many photos of food are contained on Instagram--now a pop-up diner in London is taking advantage of this new trend by letting people settle the bill for their meals simply by uploading photos of their dishes to social networks. I always thought people's taking pictures of their food was kind of silly, but at this new pop-up restaurant in the UK,I'd probably do it too.\"The Picture House\"is the world's first pay-by-photo restaurant--you order, click a photo of the food,share on Instagram and eat for free! The resta...\n\nQ: Which of the following can serve as the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Pay by Picture", "The Pop-up Diner", "No Need to Pay", "Food for Life"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2285, "question": "From their beginnings New England towns had a special democratic system of government. At a stated time all the citizens would assemble at a town meeting, where they would discuss local problems and express opinions freely. They also elected the town's officials at these gatherings and made decisions about the taxes they would pay and about other community matters. These meetings were usually held at the town hall, which was located in the central square. In the eighteenth-century town meetings, only men who owned property and who were church members actually voted, although everyone present was allowed to express their opinions. Later, all citizens were allowed to vote. Thus the town meeting became truly democratic. Town meetings are still common in New England communities. In recent year...\n\nQ: At a town meeting, people do the following things EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["express their opinions about the government", "elect officials of the towns", "make a decision about whom they should marry", "discuss some community matters"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 564, "question": "Culture helps human societies survive in changing natural environment.For example, the end of the last Ice Age, beginning about 15,000 years ago, brought a big challenge to which humans had to adapt.Before this time, large parts of the northern hemisphere were covered in great sheets of ice that contained much of the earth' s water.In North America, large animals that wandered the vast tundra provided people with food and materials for clothing and simple shelters.When the earth became warm, large Ice Age animals disappeared, and many land areas were covered by rising sea levels from melting ice.But people survived, they developed new technologies and learned how to survive on new plant and animal species. Finally some people settled into permanent villages, durable houses and farms. Cultu...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the problem caused by cultural adaptation according to the passage?", "options": ["A very developed culture came into being.", "New technologies have been developed.", "Natural resources have been used up.", "Human activities have done damage to the balance of nature."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1778, "question": "Shoplifting is happening in stores or supermarkets throughout the world. However, shoplifting happens more in British stores, according to a recent research, by the UK-based Center for Retail Research. Napoleon once considered prefix = st1 /Britainas \"a nation of shopkeepers\", to which so many people dreamed of traveling. Now it seems it is a nation of shoplifters. According to the research,Britainis the most light-fingered country in Europe, with nearly one in every two cases of shoplifting across the continent taking place in British stores. The report said there were nearly 566,000 reported cases of shoplifting inBritainout of a Europe-wide total of 1.27 million. The next worst countries in Europe,FranceandGermany, came well belowBritainwith only 188,000 and 167,000 cases, respectively....\n\nQ: By saying \"a nation of shopkeepers\". Napoleon probably meant that   _  .", "options": ["Britain was a nation of shoplifters though it was rich then", "Britain should have cared more about its agriculture", "Britain's economy was experiencing a great development", "Britainshould take some measures to reduce the number of shops"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2149, "question": "Many parents watch the news or other shows as children play nearby. But new research shows that even when the television is just background noise,it may be to a child's normal development. It's estimated that 75 percent of very young children in the United States live in homes where the television is on most of the time,even though the kids often aren't watching it. The University of Massachusetts researchers recently studied how TV background noise might affect young children. The study looked at 50 1,2and 3yearolds. Each child came to a lab with a parent and was allowed to play for an hour with various toys. For half the time,a television was on in the room,showing the adult game show as well as advertisements. During the other half hour,the TV was turned off. As expected,the children pa...\n\nQ: What does the study show?", "options": ["Children pay much attention to adult TV shows.", "Children should be allowed to watch TV for kids only.", "The background TV noise affects children's ability to focus.", "The more toys a child has,the shorter time he plays with each one."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2656, "question": "As the new semester begins, millions of college students across the country are trying hard to remember how best to write a paper or, more likely, how best to delay that paper. Procrastination is the thief of time and a lot of students suffer from it. They can spend whole days in the library doing nothing but staring into space, eating snacks, surfing the Internet, watching videos and looking at other students sitting around them, who, most likely, are doing nothing either. Paralyzed by their habit to procrastinate, they write micro blogs about their fears, asking their online friends if they sometimes have the same issue. But this does nothing to break the spell . According to a recent report, 95 percent of us procrastinate at some point and 20 percent of the world's population are always...\n\nQ: Which behavior belongs to procrastination?", "options": ["Never dream away the time.", "Always complete the tasks ahead of time.", "Never put off till tomorrow what should be done today.", "Always wait to work until the \"good mood\" or \"good time\"."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3271, "question": "If you have been joining in chat room conversations, or trading email with web pals , you have become one of the millions who write in a peculiarly short form of English. And you've got a sense of humor about short forms like SOHF (=\" sense\" of humor failure) to describe Internet newcomers who don't understand you. Across the globe, every night teenagers and their elders are \"talking online\", many of them all talking at the same time. It's fast: try talking to six people at once.It's brief: three or four words per exchange.It takes wit, concentration, and quick fingers. And it requires tremendous linguistic economy .There's neither time nor space for explanations.Why consume precious key-strokes telling six friends you have to leave for a moment to take care of your little brother when BRB...\n\nQ: If you get 17/F/NY as an answer to your A/S/L, it means   _   .", "options": ["the person on the other end is 17 from New York and he is fine", "you are talking to a girl who is 17 and lives in New York", "you are talking to 17 girls who are from New York", "the person who you are talking to is a 17-foot tall New York girl"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1018, "question": "A group of graduates, well established in their careers, were talking at a reunion and decided to visit their old university professor, now retired. During their visit, the conversation turned to complaints about stress in their work and lives. Offering his guests hot chocolate, the professor went into the kitchen and returned with a large pot of hot chocolate and other things including cups-porcelain , glass, crystal, some plain looking, some expensive, some elegant -- telling them to help themselves to the hot chocolate. When they all had a cup of hot chocolate in hand, the professor said: \"I notice that all the nice looking and expensive cups were taken, leaving behind the plain and cheap ones. While it is normal for you to want only the best for yourselves, that is the source of your p...\n\nQ: Why did the professor offer them different cups?", "options": ["Because cups were not enough for everyone.", "Because cups were beautiful.", "Because the professor wanted to teach them something.", "Because hot chocolate should be contained in different cups."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2782, "question": "Elephants scored a big win in Dohar, Qatar, on March 22, 2010. Representatives from 175 countries met in the Middle Eastem country. They voted to continue a ban on the sale of ivory . Two African nations, Tanzania and Zambia, had asked to open up the ivory trade. People feared that weakening a 21-year-old ban on the sale of ivory would encourage illegal hunting and hurt elephant populations. African elephants once numbered in the millions. Today, there are fewer than 500,000. \"People born in 100 years should be able to see an elephant,\" said Noah Wekesa, Kenya's minister of forest and wildlife. His country voted to keep the ban. In the 1980s, as many as 1 million elephants were killed throughout Africa. Hunters killed the animals for their ivory tusks, which were used to make jewelry and o...\n\nQ: Ivory is known as \"white gold\" because", "options": ["it is as rare as white gold", "it is being sold illegally", "it looks like white gold", "it is extremely valuable"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 609, "question": "Sir Steven Redgrave Winner of 5 Olympic Gold Medals \"In 1997 I was found to have developed diabetes . Believing my career was over, I felt extremely low. Then one of the specialists said there was no reason why I should stop training and competing. That was it -- the encouragement I needed. I could still be a winner if I believed in myself. I am not saying that it isn't difficult sometimes. But I wanted to prove to myself that I wasn't finished yet. Nothing is to stand in my way.\" Karen Pickering Swimming World Champion \"I swim 4 hours a day, 6 days a week. I manage that sort of workload by putting it on top of my diary. This is the key to success -- you can't follow a career in any field without being well-organized. List what you believe you can achieve. Trust yourself, write down your g...\n\nQ: What does Karen Pickering put on top of her diary?", "options": ["Her daily happenings.", "Her training schedule.", "Her achievements.", "Her sports career."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2061, "question": "It was time for a school holiday and I was at home. My family's house was located in an area by the sea. I just sat down in front of the television. Suddenly I heard a loud noise and then the first shock started to hit. My mom and I ran to the front door. We got out and we were standing in the street holding on to each other to stand up. The ground was covered with snow. I could remember watching black cracks in the earth snaking their way along the ground. A tree in our back yard was actually cut in half. As suddenly as the earthquake started, it was over. Dead silence. Then a light snow began to fall. All the power was off--no radio, no TV and no communication with the outside world. We found out later that the ground area was lowered an average of 35 feet. My dad succeeded in getting ho...\n\nQ: In which season did the earthquake take place?", "options": ["Spring.", "Summer.", "Autumn.", "Winter."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1694, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time. _ Verona De Tessant (Maya Rudolph) and Burt Farlander (John Krasinski) are in their early thirties and struggling to meet daily needs and build fulfilling lives as an artist and a salesman. When they learn they will soon become parents, they are faced with the challenge of how and where to raise a child and build a happy family. With a baby on his way, the young couple, look at their lives and are puzzled about what they really want. _ Lynn was married to Pual, but they broke up and Lynn took their daughter Alice while Paul got their son Dylan. Years later, now Dylan is getting married, and Lynn is attending the wedding, with her younger son Elliot and Ben. Elliot is a drug...\n\nQ: What is the ending of The Shawshank Redemption?", "options": ["Andy killed his wife and his wife's lover.", "Andy became famous for helping Red.", "Red felt cheated by Andy in a way.", "Red and Andy got reunited happily."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2045, "question": "When a child is told he is \"uncool\", it can be very painful. He may say he doesn't care, and even act in ways that are opposite of cool on purpose. But ultimately, these are simply ways to handle sadness by pretending it's not there. Helping a child feel better in school had to be careful. If you say, \"Why are you worried about what other children think about you? It doesn't matter!\" Children know that it does matter. Instead, an active way may be best. You could say, \"I'm going to do a couple of things for you to help you feel better in school.\" If a boy is having trouble making friends, the teacher can help him. The teacher can arrange things so that he has chances to use his abilities to contribute to class projects. This is how the other children learn how to value his good qualities a...\n\nQ: A teacher can help an unpopular child by   _  .", "options": ["seeing the child as the teacher's favourite", "asking the child to do something for partners", "forcing other children to make friends with the child", "offering the child chances to show his good qualities"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1097, "question": "College visits are important.Before you commit years of your life and money to a school, be sure you're choosing a place,\" that is a good match for your personality and interests.You can't get the \"feel' of a school from any guidebook, so be sure to visit the campus.Below are a few tips for getting the most out of your college visit. 1.Explore on your own Of course you should take the official campus tour, but be sure to allow time to hang around on your own. The trained tour guides will show you a school's selling points.But the 1dest and prettiest buildings don't give you the entire picture of a college.Try to walk the extra mile and get the complete picture of the campus. 2.Read the Bulletin Boards When you visit the student center, academic buildings and residence hall, take a few minu...\n\nQ: To get a real idea of the college during a visit, it's best to talk to  _  .", "options": ["famous professors", "campus tour guides", "admission officers", "random students"], "answer": 3}]